

pranavraval23@gmail.com

kadi

modasa

9558824405

WORK EXPERIENCE

Electrical Engineer Corel Pharma Chem

06/2019 - Present pharma company

Achievements/Tasks

- All electrical work are done under my observation.

Contact: Jignesh limbachiya - 9638331693

EDUCATION

BECHELOR OF ENGINEER

Government Engineering College Modasa

06/2015 - 05/2019

Courses

- electrical

SKILLS

Hands on knowledge of electrical equipments like controller, sensor, relays etc.

problem solving skills

basic circuit knowledge

basic knowledge of the plc

nowledge of the ac drives

working on a SCADA and HMI system.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Electrical maintenance (06/2019 - Present)

- Responsibility for observing the team of electrician.
- weekly and monthly check all major equipments like chiller, air compressor, dg set and coldstorages.
- Responsibility for the transformer and HT and LT panels.
- knowledge of the ac-dc drives and servo motors.
- knowledge of the motor repairing.

DUTIES

Supervision (06/2019 - Present)

Supervisory and undertaking electrical work within short time .troubleshooting the machine and finding fault .

LANGUAGES

English

Hindi

Full Professional Proficiency

Full Professional Proficiency

Gujarati

Full Professional Proficiency

PERSONAL SUMMARY

A self motivated and passionate electrical engineer who has experienced of all aspects of jobs on site, including very good in a quality and safety parameters. my key strength is fault finding and repairs the machinery. good in control and power system also know the fire system.